Guide to the Redtape Archive ca. 1972-1992 (Bulk 1982-1992) MSS.088
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize - Series II: Art/Comix
  - Oversize - Subseries B: Copy
    - Tom Marsan (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Calvin Reid (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Michael Roman - (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Marguerite Van Cook (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Jack Vengrow (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified (Oversized +), undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Oversize - Series III: Photography
  - Eder (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Tom Ladd (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Joseph Nechvatal - 1 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Joseph Nechvatal - 2 of 2 (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Oversize - Series IV: Production Files
  - Redtape 2 - Assemblages (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Redtape 6 - 1 Copy (Oversized +), undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Redtape 6 -General (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Redtape 6 - the galley (Oversized +), undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Redtape 7 - General (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Oversize - Series V: Events
  - General (Oversized+), undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Oversize - Series VI: Miscellaneous
  - Newspaper Clippings (Oversized), undated (Box 4, Folder 11)